<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<Snapshots Version="1.0">
    <Snapshot>
        <Title>Untitled Snapshot</Title>
        <Date>2015-08-02 13:12:07 +0200</Date>
        <Comments>
            <Comment ID="08B472CF-CE94-431C-A640-63284A68FF9B" Footnote="Yes" Color="0.85 0.85 0.85"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1404\cocoasubrtf120
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 Verdana;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs20 \cf0 Irrational entrepreneurs would probably have an even greater incentive to force creditors to accept a loss. Creditors are generally "faceless"---markets, banks or large lending institutions---so exploiting one does not evoke the same moral code as when dealing with people who make personal loans (STUDY). Moreover, a failed business affects more than just the entrepreneurs pocketbook. It affects, among other things, his pride, sense of self-worth and standing within his community [][#Kahneman2011].}]]></Comment>
            <Comment ID="C13077DE-CAAD-4873-8849-6856B9C65F31" Footnote="Yes" Color="0.85 0.85 0.85"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1404\cocoasubrtf120
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 Verdana;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs20 \cf0 Additionally, receivership, previously a common feature in many common law jurisdiction, has been on the wane. Several recent legislative reforms have either scraped it (X) or weakened it (U.K.). See [][Receivership] for a full discussion.}]]></Comment>
            <Comment ID="A701A90A-6C05-424E-92B1-BF3F9D1209C6" Footnote="Yes" Color="0.85 0.85 0.85"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1404\cocoasubrtf120
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 Verdana;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs20 \cf0 If $Y=0$ $V_1^B=qV_1^C+(1-q)V_1^L$ which is less than $V_1^L$ for viable firms. From limited liability $V_1^B\\ge C_1^B>V_1^C$.}]]></Comment>
            <Comment ID="9A3160B6-E352-4D00-9770-7267C83C81D3" Footnote="Yes" Color="0.85 0.85 0.85"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1404\cocoasubrtf120
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 Verdana;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs20 \cf0 If creditors sometimes "bribe" entrepreneurs to voluntarily liquidate, moral hazard from bankruptcy and violations to absolute priority decline. See Footnote <!--\\ref\{fnm:fn1\}--> for a discussion.}]]></Comment>
        </Comments>
    </Snapshot>
    <Snapshot>
        <Title>Untitled Snapshot</Title>
        <Date>2015-08-03 14:06:22 +0200</Date>
        <Comments>
            <Comment ID="A6091A67-AE8E-4E8B-84CD-4E03582A5B10" Footnote="Yes" Color="0.85 0.85 0.85"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1404\cocoasubrtf120
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 Verdana;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs20 \cf0 As shown in the next paper, judicial errors should also be encouraged.}]]></Comment>
            <Comment ID="AFCB83E8-AF6D-4014-95B6-0B993985D50F" Footnote="Yes" Number="36" Color="0.85 0.85 0.85"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1404\cocoasubrtf120
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 Verdana;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs20 \cf0 When the market for machines is insufficiently differentiated, some non-viable firms are always at risk of filing for bankruptcy when initial earnings are very low---and a fraction of those may be inefficiently continued due to judicial error. Nevertheless, sub-optimal interim decisions are infrequent. Firms opt for bankruptcy in only a narrow set of mathematical circumstances predicated mostly by dismal initial earnings. When low earnings are improbable, $D$ will be low squeezing the range of $X_1$ that make bankruptcy attractive. When they are likely, firms may get credit at some $D$ such that $\\ol C_0=K_0$. In this case, however, bankruptcy is not much worse than liquidation, so either the difference between returns in liquidation and those in continuation are small or judicial likelihood of liquidation is high. If, on the other hand, no such $D$ is available, the firm only gets credit at an exorbitant rate ([](#prop2)(ii)), thus guaranteeing an efficient outcome at time 1.}]]></Comment>
            <Comment ID="29DC4083-0CE0-4ED7-BE6E-2CD56F1D4E42" Footnote="Yes" Number="38" Color="0.85 0.85 0.85"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1404\cocoasubrtf120
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 Verdana;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs20 \cf0 No U.S. Chapter 11 rule implicitly reduces future earnings or explicitly prioritises equity, suggesting that the structure of Chapter 11 probably isn't the main cause of absolute priority deviations and credit-rationing[#Bebchuk2002]; the massive fees (and their priority over debt) inherent in the U.S. legal system are.}]]></Comment>
            <Comment ID="C4878A74-B1C2-4B77-836B-1208C115CC85" Footnote="Yes" Number="39" Color="0.85 0.85 0.85"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1404\cocoasubrtf120
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 Verdana;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs20 \cf0 An automatic stay is a court order that prevents confiscating collateral or collecting debt payments. It is the defining characteristic of reorganisation, since without it nothing legally prevents creditors from *de facto* liquidating an insolvent firm by seizing the assets it needs to operate.}]]></Comment>
            <Comment ID="9486350E-0AF4-46A3-8CA4-02486B2884DF" Footnote="Yes" Number="40" Color="0.85 0.85 0.85"><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\ansicpg1252\cocoartf1404\cocoasubrtf120
{\fonttbl\f0\fnil\fcharset0 Verdana;}
{\colortbl;\red255\green255\blue255;}
\pard\tx560\tx1120\tx1680\tx2240\tx2800\tx3360\tx3920\tx4480\tx5040\tx5600\tx6160\tx6720\pardirnatural

\f0\fs20 \cf0 If reorganisation is costless, automatic stays have no effect on lending beyond making it slightly more expensive. Their presence, however, will always induce firms that ought to liquidate to instead file for bankruptcy when initial earnings are very low. Since a fraction of those firms inefficiently continue due to judicial error, eliminating automatic stays is still a socially optimal action.}]]></Comment>
        </Comments>
    </Snapshot>
</Snapshots>